<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RoomDatabase</string>
    <string name="update_message">Are you sure you want to update this user?</string>
    <string name="acerca_de">About</string>
    <string name="formato_tarjeta_incorrecto">Some of the fields may be incorrect</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="addTarjeta">Add credit card</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="compartir">Share</string>
    <string name="configuracion">Settings</string>
    <string name="empty_fields">You must fill all the fields</string>
    <string name="fecha_caducidad">Expiration Date</string>
    <string name="name">name</string>
    <string name="suffixCorreo">\@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nombre">Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="emailConfirmation">I agree that I want to receive news on my email address</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="anterior">PREVIOUS</string>
    <string name="siguiente">NEXT</string>
    <string name="_uno">1</string>
    <string name="formatoIncorrectoEmail">The email\'s format is incorrect</string>
    <string name="camposVaciosError">You can\'t leave empty fields</string>
    <string name="errorEmail">The specified email has already been registered with another account</string>
    <string name="error_campos_vacios">Some fields haven\'t been filled</string>
    <string name="error_formato_email">The email\'s format is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_al_guardar_persona">Error adding a person</string>
    <string name="persona_guardada">Person added successfully</string>
    <string name="error_persona_no_existe">The person you\'re trying to delete doesn\'t exist</string>
    <string name="error_al_eliminar_persona">The person can\'t be deleted</string>
    <string name="persona_eliminada">Person deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="error_no_hay_mas_personas">There are no more people</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recicler">RecyclerActivity</string>
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="verLista">See list</string>
    <string name="SI">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="persona_no_actualizada">The person wasn\'t updated</string>
    <string name="empty_password">If you leave password filled empty, the current one will be used</string>
    <string name="tarjeta_guardada">Card added successfully</string>
    <string name="error_al_guardar_tarjeta">Error adding a card</string>
    <string name="numero_tarjeta">Card Number</string>
    <string name="CVV">CVV</string>
    <string name="verTarjetas">See all cards</string>
    <string name="mes">Month</string>
    <string name="n_tarjeta_helper">Length: 16 characters</string>
    <string name="cvv_helper">Example: 123</string>
    <string name="pedir_cita">Book appointment</string>
    <string name="ver_citas">See appointments</string>
    <string name="opciones">Options</string>
    <string name="inicio_sesion">Log in</string>
    <string name="salud_madrid">Application</string>
    <string name="hora_de_la_cita">Time</string>
    <string name="fecha_de_la_cita">Date</string>
    <string name="idcita">AppointmentID</string>
    <string name="cerrarSesion">Log out</string>
    <string name="verRepositorio">See repository</string>
    <string name="revisar_citas">Check appointments</string>
    <string name="marcar_cita">Mark as completed</string>
    <string name="seleccione_una_especialidad">Select a field</string>
    <string name="noticias">News</string>
    <string name="logo_salud_madrid">Logo Salud Madrid</string>
    <string name="Inicio">Main screen</string>
    <string name="noticiaDoctor">Dear colleagues,  I hope this message finds you well. I wanted to inform you about some changes that will be implemented in our hospital starting next week.  First of all, we have decided to extend the operating hours of our emergency department. From now on, it will be available 24/7. This measure has been taken with the goal of improving the care we provide to our patients and being able to attend any emergency quickly and efficiently.  Secondly, we have hired two new doctors to reinforce our team. They are both professionals with extensive experience in the field of internal medicine and they will be willing to collaborate with all of you on any project where you may need their help.  Finally, I wanted to remind you of the importance of keeping your knowledge up to date and continuing to train in your area of specialization. We know that the world of medicine is very dynamic and that new advances and techniques are constantly emerging. That is why it is essential that we stay aware of the latest developments and continue learning in order to provide the best care to our patients.  I hope these measures will contribute to improving the quality of care we provide in our hospital and make our work more efficient and satisfying. If you have any suggestions or ideas that you think might be useful, do not hesitate to share them with us.  Thank you for your dedication and effort during these challenging times. Together, we can continue to do great work for the benefit of our patients.  Sincerely, the Hospital Director</string>
    <string name="comunicado">Official Statement</string>
    <string name="noticiaUsuario">One news item that has been very present in recent months in relation to health is the COVID-19 pandemic. This is an infectious disease caused by the SARS-CoV-2 coronavirus, which was first transmitted to humans in Wuhan, China, in 2019. Since then, the pandemic has spread worldwide, affecting millions of people and causing thousands of deaths.  To combat the pandemic, governments and health authorities have implemented measures such as confinement, social distancing, and the use of masks. In addition, several vaccines against the coronavirus have been developed and distributed around the world. Despite this, the pandemic is still a global problem and new cases and variants of the virus continue to appear.  COVID-19 has had a great impact on the mental health of the population, as isolation and fear of contracting the disease can cause anxiety, depression, and other mental disorders. That is why it is important for people to take care of their mental health during the pandemic and seek professional support if needed.  In summary, the COVID-19 pandemic has been one of the greatest health crises in recent times, affecting both the physical and mental health of people. Although vaccines have been developed and measures have been taken to control the virus, there is still much work to be done to overcome this crisis and protect the health of the population.</string>
    <string name="noCitas">You haven\'t booked any appointment.</string>
    <string name="noCitasRevisar">You don\'t have any appointments to check</string>
    <string name="marcar_como_atendida">Mark as attended</string>
    <string name="seleccione_una_fecha">Select a date</string>
    <string name="seleccione_un_doctor">Select a doctor</string>
    <string name="seleccione_una_hora">Select a time</string>
    <string name="dra_isabel">Dra. Isabel</string>
    <string name="dr_juan">Dr. Juan</string>
    <string name="dr_nefario">Dr. Nefario</string>
    <string name="info">Information</string>
    <string name="conoce_a_nuestros_doctores">Know our doctors</string>
</resources>